falconsocial.com 2017-07-02

# Privacy Policy | Falcon.io

**1\. Preamble**

This Privacy Policy covers the collection, processing and storage of Personally Identifiable Information (“PII” or “Personal Information”) by Falcon.io ApS and its subsidiaries (“Falcon.io”), and the individual (“You” or “Your”) making use of the Falcon.io Website(s), Falcon.io’s pages on social media channels, the Falcon.io Platform and The Falcon.io applications (e.g. mobile Apps) (hereafter collectively referred to as the “Services”).

For clarification, Personal Information may be defined as any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person; an identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity. E.g. name, address, e-mail or phone number.

**2\. Applicability**

  1. This Privacy Policy applies to the information as described in the Preamble, and is not applicable to Personal Information collected through unrelated third parties or other sources. 
  2. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the customer content or data, which a customer or their third party providers provide to Falcon.io in order for Falcon.io to provide its Services to customers (“Customer Content”). Processing of “Customer Content” is governed by the agreement between Falcon.io and its customer, and Falcon.io is a “Data Processor” in relation such Customer Content.

**3\. General principles**

You should be expecting the following:

  1. _Collection:_ Falcon.io will only collect and process Personal Information for purposes that are explicitly stated and factual. Furthermore, Falcon.io only processes Personal Information which is relevant and necessary to fulfill the purposes of the collection. See article 4 below. 
  2. _Quality:_ Falcon.io will take appropriate steps to ensure that no false or misleading information will be processed. 
  3. _Storage:_ Falcon.io will only store your Personal Information as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes of the collection, or as permitted by law. 
  4. _Access:_ Upon request from you, and as required by law, Falcon.io will provide you with access to the data so any inaccuracies can be corrected. 
  5. _Security:_ Falcon.io will take appropriate technical, physical and organizational measures to protect the Personal Information from destruction, loss, misuse, reduction of quality, unauthorized access or disclosure or from being processed in a non­compliant matter. 
  6. _Third parties:_ Falcon.io does not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personal Information, however Falcon.io may use partners/subcontractors (third parties, including our affiliates), to store and process your Personal Information. In case such subcontractor and partner processes any Personal Information collected from you, the subcontractors and partners are subject to the same level of data protection as expected by Falcon.io. 
  7. _Third Country Transfers:_ You understand that Falcon.io may transfer your Personal Information in and to the United States and other countries and territories outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). In case of such transfer to non-EEA countries, Falcon.io will ensure that the Personal Information is adequately protected and processed in accordance with the purpose as set forth herein.

**4\. What information does Falcon.io collect?**

  1. _Types of information collected by Falcon.io when using the Services  
_ Falcon.io will collect certain Personal Information on you in connection with the use of the Services. This is done in order to ensure the proper functioning of the Services and provides better insight on your use of the Services. The Personal Information collected includes, but is not limited to, the following: 
    1. Name, user name, unique user ID, e-­mail address, IP-address, device information (hardware and software, e.g. browser and operating system), mailing address, city, state, country, approximate geographical location, title, passwords, phone numbers, click and movement tracking, actions performed in the Services, content uploaded or written in the Services, cookies information, internal management groups, access level of users and other monitoring of use of the Services’ features.

**5\. Why does Falcon.io collect Personal Information and what is it used for?**

  1. _General use-cases  
_ Falcon.io generally collects Personal Information for the following purposes: 
    * To operate the Services and ensure proper functionality of the Services
    * To allow users to access and log in to the Services
    * To improve the Services and provide users of the Services a better experience
    * To collect statistics and metrics on use of the Services by analyzing individuals’ use and behavior
    * To allow you to contact Falcon.io, e.g. for support requests via chat or e-mail functionalities
    * To provide you with downloadable content, such as case studies
    * To provide you with periodic e-mails containing market and product news 
  2. _Elaboration on collections and purpose hereof_  
You understand, that Falcon.io will monitor the use of the Services and collect Personal Information on your use. Falcon.io may analyze the use of the Services, user behavior and the collected Personal Information in order to improve its content and services. Falcon.io may, for the duration of the use of the Services and hereafter, as permitted under applicable law, store the information collected on you and logs from the use of the Services. 

In addition to this, Falcon.io may use the Personal Information in an aggregate and anonymous manner, e.g. by compiling statistical and performance information related to the provision and operation of the Services. You understand that Falcon.io may use and publicly publish aggregated and anonymous information, provided that such information is not considered Personal Information. Falcon.io retains all rights in such results in aggregated and anonymized information (Falcon.io does not assume rights over its customers’ intellectual property right protected content). 

The Services may use _“cookies”_ , pieces of information that Falcon.io’s webserver sends to your computer’s browser file. When you return, Falcon.io’s or a partner’s site it will detect whether you have one of Falcon.io’s cookies on your computer. Falcon.io’s cookies help provide additional functionality to the Service and helps Falcon.io to analyze Service usage more accurately. For instance, the Services may set a cookie on your browser that keeps you from needing to enter a password more than once during a visit to the site. 

When visiting Falcon.io’s websites, Falcon.io may also place third party Cookies, which are used for marketing purposes. Falcon.io and its partners use these cookies, in order to deliver relevant marketing content to you when you visit Falcon.io’s or third parties’ websites. 

The Falcon.io Services use Google Analytics for collecting cookie and usage data. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the information collected to track and examine the use of the Services, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. For the browser opt-out please visit: <http://fal.cn/QTTp>. 

To see other cookies Falcon.io uses and places when you visit the Services, please visit: [www.falcon.io/cookie-policy](https://www.falcon.io/cookie-policy/) 

The Services may use a technology known as web beacons, also known as single­pixel gifs, ­that allow this site to collect web log information. A web beacon is a graphic on a web page or in an e-­mail message designed to track pages viewed or messages opened. Web log information is gathered when you visit the Services by the computer that hosts Falcon.io’s website (this is called a “webserver”). The webserver automatically recognizes some non­-personal information, such as the date and time you visited this site, the pages you visited, the website you came from, the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, and the domain name and address of your Internet service provider (e.g., AOL). Falcon.io may also include web beacons in e-­mail messages in order to determine whether messages have been opened. 

The Services may use a technology called _javascript_ , that allows Falcon.io to collect information on your interaction with the Services, such as click-tracking, to determine popular functionalities and malfunctions of the Services.

**6\. Job postings and applications on Falcon.io’s webpage**

If you choose to apply for a job at Falcon.io, and submit Personal Information, such as a resume and motivated application, through the Falcon.io webpage(s), Falcon.io will make use of a third party provider to store and process the application. Falcon.io shall only retain such data for a duration as permissible in accordance with applicable law.

**7\. Disclosure of Personal Information**

  1. Except as set forth in this agreement, Falcon.io will not disclose or share your Personal Information with third parties. However, Falcon.io may disclose or share Personal Information if 
    * You request Falcon.io to do so
    * You have consented to such disclosure to a third party
    * Falcon.io is required to do so by law, or as required by administrative or court order
    * Falcon.io needs to defend, protect or exercise its legal rights, or to defend
    * Falcon.io against legal claims or demands
    * Falcon.io is acquired by or merged with another company 
  2. Notwithstanding article 7.1, Falcon.io will use partners and subcontractors as set forth in article 3.7 above. These partners and subcontractors may be CRM-providers for current and prospective customers, data analytics providers analyzing data from our Services, Content Marketing System providers assisting e-mail and promotional campaigns and other marketing assistance. Such third parties shall only use such Personal Information in order to provide their services to Falcon.io.

**8\. Right to information, correction, deletion and retention**

In accordance with the ‘Danish Act on Processing of Personal Data’ and privacy policies of certain third party service providers, Falcon.io will give individuals information on the Personal Information processed about the individual, if the individual requests such information. Falcon.io may, as permitted by applicable law, claim a reasonable fee for such request.

Individuals can object to a processing of a specific piece of Personal Information. Falcon.io shall assess such objection and if the objection is justified, Falcon.io shall cease the processing of the Personal Information in question.

A registered individual can at any time request for Personal Information to be corrected, deleted or blocked if he/she finds it to be misleading or being processed in violation with applicable law.

The above only applies to Personal Information where Falcon.io is considered the data controller or where Falcon.io is obliged to make such remedies available in accordance with use rights granted by third parties.

Requests should be sent to privacy@falcon.io and should in general contain the following information:

  1. Your name, address, phone number and e-­mail address
  2. What your request concerns (insight, correction, deletion or blocking)
  3. The type of data concerned and where it originates from 

Falcon.io will retain certain Personal Information for other lawful purposes, such as compliance with legal requirements, compliance with terms and conditions and defense against claims. You may therefore experience that Falcon.io will not delete all Personal Information, until such information no longer can be retained in order to fulfil or safeguard Falcon.io’s legal interest and obligations.

**9\. Minors**

The Services are not intended to be used by, or designed to attract, individuals under the age of 15. Falcon.io does not collect Personal Information from any person Falcon.io actually knows is an individual under the age of 15. Please be advised that the minimum age required to consent to collection of Personal Information may vary from country to country, and you are not to access or use the Services if you are not of age to share such Personal Information with Falcon.io.

**10\. Third party websites and content**

While you are using the Services, you may be presented with links leading to third party websites or content. Please be aware, that such third party websites are outside of Falcon.io’s control, and are subject to that third party’s own privacy policy. Falcon.io is not responsible for such third party’s practices and cannot guarantee or represent the security of such third party’s website. Furthermore, Falcon.io cannot guarantee the correctness of information on such third party’s website.

**11\. Questions**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us directly:

_EU and rest of the world:_   
Falcon.io ApS   
Attn: Legal   
H.C. Andersens boulevard 27, 1st floor   
1553 Copenhagen V   
Denmark

Registration no.: 3336 2226   
E-mail: privacy@falcon.io

_United States of America:  
_ Falcon Social, Inc. doing business as Falcon.io   
134 North 4th Street, 2nd floor   
Brooklyn, New York 11249

Note that the website www.falcon.io is administered and provided by the company Falcon.io ApS, and requests relating to information collected on the website shall be directed to that company.

**12\. Changes**

Falcon.io reserves the right to amend and update the Privacy Policy from time to time. The last updated Privacy Policy available on this website will always be the applicable policy. Please revisit the website frequently to be aware of updates and changes.
